A Guide to the Farrier Family Papers, 1894-1972
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 11, 1905-1938 (Box 11)
  - Gilmer, R. C., March 1927.
  - Gertrude Hale v. Tom Hale, April-June 1927.
  - Leona Henry v. Walter Henry, December 1927-February 1928.
  - Hambrick, G. E. and wife, April 1926-October 1927.
  - W. L. Hunt and Co., April-July 1927.
  - Huff and Cook v. Giles Lumber Co., March 1924.
  - J. W. T. Henderson v. Commonwealth, November 1922-November 1923.
  - William Smith v. Otis Hopkins, c. September 1925.
  - Haley and Moran (2 files), March 1918-December 1922.
  - H. W. Hale, December 1919-May 1923.
  - James Hoge, et al, v. Kirk and Williams, August 1917.
  - Annie M. Honaker, Guardian, v. D. T. Tolbert, et al, February-May 1924.
  - C. A. Hoilman, et al v. S. S. Lafon and Co., March 1924-December 1924.
  - Ira C. Hale v. Lydia Dunbar, May 1923-July 1925.
  - Claims v. W. L. Hunt and Co., November 1925-October 1926.
  - Hubbard Oven Co. v. Turner Bros., October 1925-February 1927.
  - Evelyn Henderson v. E. M. Henderson, September 1925.
  - Harris, T. S. v. Johnson, H., October 1924-March 1926.
  - D. W. Holt and wife v. Q. P. Albert, October 1921-September 1923.
  - Highway Commission v. C. C. Farley, May-August 1927.
  - Highway Commission v. A. B. Glenn, et al, April-June 1927.
  - Highway Commission v. C. R. Smith, September 1925-June 1926.
  - Highway Commission v. G. E. and Sallie Hambrick, August 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. Georgia and Jessie Lamb, July-August 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. Orrie O. Thomas, July-August 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. W. R. Walker, August-October 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. Shumate and Walker, August-October 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. A. E. Shumate, August 1925-April 1926.
  - Highway Commission v. Susan H. Smith, August-October 1925.
  - Highway Commission v. E. A. Keister, March 1926-May 1927.
- Box 12 1908-1930 (Box 12)
  - Highway Commission v. A. H. Price, May-October 1926.
  - Highway Commission v. Charlotte Wells, July 1925-July 1927.
  - Highway Commission v. Sue Cooper, et al, November 1925-July 1926.
  - Highway Commission v. H. G. Johnston, August 1925-April 1930.
  - Highway Commission v. E. H. Johnston, et al, September 1927-September 1928.
  - Highway Commission v. G. W. Breedlove, August 1925-April 1926.
  - G. G. Johnson, 1907, March-October 1922.
  - H. B. Johnston v. C. H. Johnston, October 1925.
  - Greasy Johnston, December 1926-February 1927.
  - R. P. Johnston v. Blankenship's, November 1923-September 1924.
  - B. T. Johnston v. C. L. Gans, et al, April 1919-August 1921.
  - C. G. Killen, March 1922.
  - I. P. King, c. March 1922.
  - Kirk, E. L., September-October 1922.
  - E. W. King Co. v. J. J. Cole, November 1921.
  - Kinnier Montgomery and Co. v. R. E. Donthat, January-February 1922.
  - W. L. Kinzie, undated.
  - Thomas Christian Kirk, February-October 1923.
  - P. H. Killey v. G. F. Moore, May-June 1926.
  - Kimbalton Store Co. v. Flat Top Auto Supply Co., January 1926-April 1927.
  - Charles A. Klotz-Phlegar and Shelton, February 1916.
  - Charles A. Klotz, April-October 1923.
  - C. W. Kelly v. C. C. Atkins, November 1922-March 1926.
  - Edward Kelly, July-August 1925.
  - Knepper and Good, July-September 1911.
  - William Lybrook v. Bertha Peery, et al, March 1925.
  - Leffell, G. W. v. the Wolf Co., October 1921-April 1923.
  - L. M. Lucas v. J. H. Hilton, October 1920-April 1921.
  - R. T. Linkous v. J. P. Stowers and wife, March 1921.
  - C. F. Linsenmeyer, March 1913-February 1917.
  - W. C. Lucas Estate, July 1924.
  - E. O. Lovell, August 1924-January 1925.
  - Mrs. F. Long, 1923.
  - Pearson Estate v. Life Insurance Co. of Virginia, August 1918-March 1927.
  - R. T. Linkous, et al v. Henry Campbell, December 1925.
  - G. M. Lamb v. Charles Lewis, March-April 1925.
  - Alice Lang v. C. W. Bishop, May-September 1926.
  - Lucas, W. C., et al v. C. D. Price, et al, June 1919-May 1924.
  - Maude McGhee v. William Fleeman, May 1930.
  - The Merriman Company, November 1911-March 1918.
  - Lucinda Murphy v. John Murphy, undated.
  - Victor Roller Mills v. J. M. Martin, June 1923.
  - Motor Supply Co. v. A. E. Williams, November 1920-November 1922.
  - Merriman Company v. Kennedy and Company, May 1911-February 1916.
  - G. M. Mitchell, April 1908-April 1918.
  - Merriman Co. v. G. M. Mitchell, November 1909-August 1914.
  - J. R. Moye v. Sallie Moye, undated.
  - Bank of Mifflinburg, Pa. v. People's Supply Company, February 1923-December 1925.
  - Marlbrook Lime Company v. Kessinger, August-October 1925.
  - Miller Bros., et al v. A. R. Porterfield Estate, January 1921-August 1926.
  - Munsey Bros.-Bland County, December 1922-October 1923.
  - Herbert W. Morris, October 1926-April 1927.
  - Motor Car Supply Co. v. Pembroke Motor Co., December 1924.
  - Dewey Martin v. Lillie Lee Martin, c. July 1921.
  - Motor Supply Co. v. G. L. Bane (S. K. Bane's administrator) and J. S. Dehart, June 1927-May 1928.
  - Lula Mullens v. N. E. Rierson, May 1925.
  - W. V. Morris-Road Matter, November 1926.
  - Mrs. C. M. Munsey v. J. W. Lucas, May 1923.
  - Bertie Musselman v. Emma Janney, February 1929-January 1930.
  - Mountain Lake Hotel Co. v. American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, July 1925-October 1926.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Giles County, October 1924-September 1939.
  - N & W Railway Co.-County Bridge, Pembroke, June 1923-February 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Giles County-Roads, November 1916-October 1917.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Boyd, February 1932-April 1933.
  - N & W Railway v. C. L. Simpkins, July-August 1917.
  - Mrs. Neal v. John Thompson, November 1925-November 1927.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. L. C. Bivens, October 1929-April 1930.
  - George Fleeman v. N & W Railway Co., September-December 1928.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. J. M. Burton, April-July 1929.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. J. R. Johnson, September 1925-March 1926.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. C. H. Johnson, February 1926-May 1927.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. George Carper (2 files), January-February, April 1927.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. S. M. Caldwell, October 1922-October 1923.
  - New River Merchantile Company, Inc., June-October 1921.
  - New River Water Diversion, February 1925.
  - J. M. Newton, January-September 1926.
  - N & W Railway Co.--Multiple cases, December 1922-June 1923.
  - Narrows v. Board of Supervisors, et al, March 1920-November 1921.
  - Narrows Lumber & Manufacturing Co. v. Dixie Manufacturing Co., May 1909-November 1910.
  - New River, Holston, & Western Railroad Co. v. Union Tanning Co., et al, September 1912-March 1913.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. E. H. Perkins, admin, September 1919-June 1922.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Emma Kessler Sweet, August 1919-September 1920.
- Box 13, 1910-1935 (Bulk, 1920-1929) (Box 13)
  - New River, Holston, & Western Railroad Co. and N & W Railway Co. v. Hubble, admin, et al, Janaury 1919-December 1920.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. A. J. Hale (S. H. Stump admin), October 1916-February 1917.
  - W. H. Buchanan v. N & W Railway Co., September 1915-October 1916.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Joseph Raflo, June-July 1916.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. A. K. Croy, October 1923-April 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Hopkins, February-March 1916.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. G. W. Echols, September 1915.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. John A. Adair, November 1915-May 1916.
  - Susan E. Sweet v. N & W Railway Co. and the Virginia Co., August-September 1912.
  - Leas & McVitty, Inc. v. N & W Railway Co., February-April 1913.
  - N & W Railway Co. Garnishee--Frank Halter v. L.Quillen Shows, August 1914.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. J. M. Killian, March-October 1912.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Annie C. French, July-November 1912.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. E. L. Poindexter, September-November 1913.
  - Mrs. Willie E. Tanner, admin, v. N & W Railway Co., July 1910-July 1912.
  - Jessie J. Lamb v. N & W Railway Co., March 1918.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. H. E. Dixon, December 1919-November 1924.
  - Eliza Vest v. N & W Railway Co., October 1921-July 1922.
  - W. L. Johnson v. N & W Railway Co., May 1923-January 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. J. E. Lucas, April-October 1924.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Eva Carter, May-November 1923.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Henry Parcell, August 1919-October 1922.
  - Julia Waldron v. N & W Railway Co., March 1922-August 1923.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. R. L. Reed (file empty).
  - N & W Railway Co. v. C. P. Painter and J. J. Lamb, November 1917-April 1918.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. C. T. Leuseumeyer (file empty).
  - Douglas Martin, admin. v. N & W Railway Co., May-July 1910.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. W. C. Simpkins, February-March 1917.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Capt. George Davis, March-August 1917.
  - New River, Holston & Western Railroad Co. v. D. E. Conley, October 1917-April 1926.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Wirt Dunford, April 1925-May 1926.
  - New River Development Co.--Maps, May 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. J. O. Smith, et al, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. H. E. Lushbough, et al, June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. E. S. Eaton, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. W. H. Hale, et al, May 1925-September 1935.
  - New River Development Co. v. D. J. Croy, et al, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co.--Correspondence, April 1925-February 1926.
  - New River Development Co. v. J. A. Davis, June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. D. F. Hale, et al, May 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Giles G. Lindsey, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. D. F. Hale, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. E. A. Hopkins, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. E. B. Eaton, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. J. W. B. Stafford, et al, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. James Stephens, et al, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. J. Hoge Robertson, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Ethel Robertson, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Raleigh Davis, et al, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. I. H. Brown, et al, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Frank E. Stafford, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Mrs. E. J. Underwood, May-June 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. J. M. Peck, et al, May-July 1925.
  - New River Development Co. v. Clara Cooper, March-April 1926.
  - New River Development Co. v. E. D. Dennis, April-July 1925.
  - Noland Company v. Narrows Heating and Plumbing Co., May 1924-September 1925.
  - Newport Merchantile Co. v. J. M. Puckett, September 1924.
  - L. P. Noel v. Gibbs, Hill, and the Virginian Railway Co., August 1925-December 1926.
- Box 14, 1910-1947 (Box 14)
  - Miller, L. L.--Various, may 1924-April 1941.
  - Miller, L.L.--Deputy Treasurer, June-July 1933.
  - L. L. Miller Estate, April-October 1943.
  - T. S. Miller v. J. S. Stevens estate, January 1924-March 1929.
  - Dr. J. W. Miller, June 1924-October 1937.
  - G. C. and J. O. Mitchell, July 1924-August 1943.
  - Misc. Papers, September 1910-July 1944.
  - Julia Martin v. Eva Martin, November 1944-December 1945.
  - L. L. Miller estate, September 1941-June 1946.
  - Mrs. Lon J. Mayberry v. Sam E. Finley, August-September 1942.
  - Town of Narrows--Bond issue, June 1931-December 1933.
  - National Builders Contracting Company, Inc., October 1933-December 1937.
  - J. H. North v. Giles County, April 1927-December 1936.
  - Narrows Water Company, June 1934-May 1937.
  - Newport-Appalachian Electric Power Co., March-October 1926.
  - N & W Railway Co.--L. E. Munsey abstract, May-December 1940.
  - N & W Railway Co.--S. S. Weis abstract, September 1929-January 1941.
  - N & W Railway Co.--R. J. McLemore abstract, May-November 1940.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Blakenship, June 1939-October 1940.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. John M. Havens, March 1939-December 1940.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. R. E. Pettit (F. R. Spender's admin), October-December 1938.
  - R. S. Oglesby estate, January 1933-December 1938.
  - Pembroke, Bank of, September 1931-May 1932.
  - Powell. H. H., January 1934-May 1935.
  - Price, Charlton, October 1935.
  - Mrs. L. M. Perdue v. E. L. Shockey, et al, October 1932-June 1936.
  - Pearisburg, National Bank of, February 1922-August 1932.
  - People's Bank of Vinton v. A. V. Snodgrass, April 1928-March 1935.
  - Price, Lucy B. estate, March 1945-February 1947.
  - Julian Radcliff estate, December 1935-December 1936.
  - James E. Stafford, January-June 1939.
  - L. B. Snidow, June 1936-June 1940.
  - Strange Mining Co., December 1934-July 1936.
  - C. M. Straley, guardian v. Elizabeth Shaffer, et al, September 1926-June 1934.
  - Smith, Eva, et al, March 1937-April 1939.
  - Commonwealth v. Star Amusement Co., September 1936-May 1939.
  - Tuggle, J. C., October 1932-December 1935.
  - Thompson, Burnard, et al v. H. W. Hale's estate, March 1914, undated.
  - E. I. Terry v. W. T. Cuddy, November 1931-December 1934.
  - O. O. Spangler, October-December 1936.
  - Virginian Railway Co., August 1934-December 1941.
  - Virginia Hardwood Lumber Co., October 1935-October 1936.
  - Vest v. Vest, December 1939-July 1946.
  - Williams, J. H., April-May 1939.
  - Wizard Bakery, Inc., January 1929-April 1935.
  - Whittaker v. Whittaker, et al, undated.
  - E. L. Wilburn, undated.
  - Whittaker, C. C. and Co., Inc., May 1933-November 1934.
- Box 15, 1854-1949 (Bulk, 1940-1949) (Box 15)
  - Atkins, Alice W., November 1943-August 1946.
  - Pilgrim Coal Co.--General, January 1941-August 1946.
  - Pilgrim Coal Co.--Title papers, April 1854-November 1934.
  - Pilgrim Coal Co. and Mullins Gas Co., July 1934-November 1942.
  - Pilgrim Coal Co., April-May 1922.
  - Price, Lucy, February 1945-April 1946.
  - Atwell, Thomas J., August 1945.
  - Airport Acres--Lots in process, November 1943.
  - Airport Acres--Titles, October 1943-April 1944.
  - Elizabeth Hensey, Admx of John L. Hensey, July 1941-December 1944.
  - Celanese Corporation of America--Fly ash opinion, May 1943.
  - Pilgrim Coal Co.--Tax matters, June 1936-December 1945.
  - Copies of deedes, contracts, mortgages, and title abstracts, October 1946-January 1948.
  - Angels Rest--Interior claims, etc. (2 files), November 1917-October 1929, undated.
  - Angels Rest--Interior tracts, May 1900-October 1917.
  - Angels Rest--Title abstracts, May 1900-October 1917.
  - New River Realty Corporation, May 1947-January 1948.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. H. H. Harless, June-October 1946.
  - N & W Railway Co.--General, May 1935-June 1946.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. Barker, May 1945-June 1946.
  - Committee for Ida, Henry, and Haley Butt, October 1944-March 1947.
  - Federal Land Bank v. John E. Wysong, et al, December 1929-February 1938.
  - Copies of wills, deeds, contracts, and title abstracts, January 1939-November 1941.
- Box 16, 1925-1949 (Box 16)
  - California Company, March 1948-September 1949.
  - Celanese Corporation, March 1937-February 1939.
  - E. W. Horton v. W. E. Jones, et al, February 1938-July 1948.
  - Coburn, W. O. and Son, September 1940.
  - New River Realty Corporation, February 1948-September 1950.
  - Copies of land grants, undated.
  - Copies of deeds, contracts, and wills, January-June 1946.
  - Gunnoe, A. H., April-July 1942.
  - Giles Construction Corporation, September-November 1943.
  - Farrier, M. P.--Cole land matter, November 1939-December 1943.
  - Giles Motor Sales, Inc., November 1937-September 1943.
  - Giles Development Corp.--Deeds of trust and contracts, October 1941-July 1945.
  - Farrier and Farrier check book, January 1944-June 1947.
  - Copies of deeds and correspondence, December 1946-April 1947.
  - Copies of deeds, contracts, and wills, August-December 1945.
  - Guthrie, W. A. & J. R., March 1941-September 1942.
  - James R. Goodwin estate, June 1925-July 1941.
  - Giles Development Corp.--Correspondence, September 1941-June 1946.
  - Andrew W. Smith, November 1945-December 1947.
  - Appalachian Electric Power Co., December 1937-July 1947.
  - Giles Development Corp.--Deeds, etc., May 1943-October 1946.
  - Giles Development Corp., October 1941-October 1943.
  - Johnson, E. H. v. Robertson, et al, February 1939-June 1941.
  - Jacobs and Blumenstiel, October 1943.
  - Hunter, Guy E., November-December 1945.
  - Hilton, Caroline--Land, December 1944.
  - Giles Development Corp.--Deeds, September 1942-December 1945.
  - A. L. Farrier, March 1944-June 1948.
  - Copies of deeds and contracts, June 1944-June 1948.
- Box 17, 1918-1944 (Bulk, 1935-1944) (Box 17)
  - Highway Department, June 1934-January 1942.
  - Johnson v. Byrnes Heirs--Title papers, March 1918-February 1919.
  - Alvis Bank Stock Case, May-November 1941.
  - Birchlawn Burial Park, Inc., January 1930-November 1933.
  - Big Stony Land--Abstracts, undated.
  - Big Stony Land--Titles, October 1939-August 1942.
  - Bank of Giles County v. Bland County Lumber Co., December 1936-July 1940.
  - Bank of Giles County v. H. B. Shelton's admin, et al, December 1932-November 1942.
  - Lacy C. Correll v. Letcher T. Correll, et al, January 1942-October 1944.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Condemnation cases, November 1936-August 1938.
  - Craig-Giles County Iron Co., January 1937-December 1939.
  - Craig-Giles County Iron Co.--Title papers, May 1935-March 1939.
  - Farrier, M. P and the Federal Forest Service, October 1942-September 1943.
  - Farrier, M. P. v. J. J. Cole (3 files), January 1937-December 1939, October 1939-August 1941, July 1941-May 1943.
  - Farmers Supply Co.--Bankruptcy, April-December 1938.
  - Federal Land Bank of Baltimore v. O. L. Williams, et al, October 1941-January 1943.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Macie Blankenship, May 1939-April 1942.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Croye, et al, June 1937-February 1942.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Charles L. Eaton's estate, May-December 1942.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Robert Blankenship, July-September 1942.
  - Federal Land Bank v. Porterfield, A. J. estate, July 1941-July 1942.
- Box 18, 1924-1944 (Bulk, 1935-1944) (Box 18)
  - Federal Farm Mortgage Corporation v. J. R. Blankenship, April-October 1942.
  - Greear, Winnie S., April 1940-October 1943.
  - Winnie S. Greear v. Ingles (2 files), April 1940-October 1943, January-February 1942.
  - Highway Department, November 1940-January 1942.
  - W. J. Henson, et al v. W. W. Shumate, et al, September 1939-September 1942.
  - Home Owners' Land Corp., October 1934-April 1935.
  - Hardware Mutual Casualty Co., March-April 1935.
  - Lake Hotel Corp., January 1937-September 1939.
  - Lindsey v. Lindsey, October 1938-December 1944.
  - Lake Hotel Corp. v. L. M. Martin, January 1939-January 1942.
  - Little Stony Game and Fish Preserve and Lake Hotel Corp., November 1930-May 1936.
  - Link v. Echols, June 1938-September 1941.
  - Marshall, H. M. v. C. F. Givens, March 1937-July 1941.
  - Miller, James Robert v. Joe Shannon, December 1937-November 1941.
  - N & W Railway Co. v. J. J. Hale, April 1941-June 1942.
  - N & W Railway Co. and Myrtle Havens, October-December 1942.
  - Pembroke Manufacturing Co., December 1924-June 1943.
  - Presbyterian Church [Pearisburg], June 1939.
  - Narrows Business Mens Club, December 1938.
  - Smith, E. L., May 1933-April 1936.
  - B. H. Spangler, guardian, et al, v. Evelyn Cooper, May 1937-May 1941.
  - Jean Spangler v. Chester P. Wright, August 1942-May 1944.
  - India Shumate, guardian v. Elizabeth Jane Dickens, et al, September 1924-January 1926.
  - James E. Spangler estate (2 files), June 1933-January 1936, July 1935-May 1936.
  - State Board of Accountancy, September-November 1943.
  - Thurman and Boone Co. v. Buchanan, et al, July 1942-April 1943.
- Box 19, 1896-1936 (Bulk, 1910-1929) (Box 19)
  - Title Guaranty Trust and Savings Bank v. J. B. Botts, et al (5 files), December 1926-August 1936, August 1932, February-April 1935, undated, October 1930-September 1932.
  - Virginia Pharmacal Corporation, June 1926-March 1928.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Federal Court papers, February 1908-January 1930.
  - Walker, W. W., Treasurer, January 1920-July 1930.
  - James H. Spangler estate--Beckett v. Spangler), January 1923-June 1925.
  - Thacker, et al v. Shaley, January 1926-January 1928.
  - B. W. White, November 1926-May 1927.
  - Sarver v. Virginian Railway Co., April-December 1929.
  - Virginian Railway Co. (file empty).
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Interior Claims, c. November 1923.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Epling case, undated.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. J. M. Kelly, December 1926-March 1929.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Goodwin, March 1918.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Jacob Epling, et al, March 1921-August 1922.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Epling and Goodwin cases, May-June 1918.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Land claims, March 1918-March 1919.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Epling, et al--Federal and Circuit Court, October 1918-April 1921.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Interior Iron Ore Corp., August 1914-January 1916.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. J. M. Kelly, July 1918-June 1928.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Juniors, February 1896-October 1932.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Wickline, et al, September-November 1919.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. J. M Kelly, April 1911-July 1929.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Jacob Epling, et al, December 1907-December 1925.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Contracts, October 1912-September 1919.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Epling, et al, June 1903-April 1906.
  - English-Ott Lumber Co., April 1920-May 1926.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co., January 1916-July 1918.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--History of Juniors, undated.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Albert, October 1913-March 1914.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Briefs, April 1919-February 1920.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co., February 1914.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co., undated.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. and Heald, April 1918-October 1928.
- Box 20, 1906-1929 (Box 20)
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co.--Letters, December 1920-August 1929.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Mrs. Vance, July 1918.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. J. B. Snidow, et al, June-September 1929.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Giles Wright--Brief and Correspondence; Record (2 files), october 1917-December 1922, October 1912-August 1919.
  - Craig-Giles Iron Co. v. Craig County Lumber Corp., November 1915-September 1916.
  - Saxon Lime and Lumber Co. v. Sarah E. L. Radford, April-May 1916.
  - Saxon Lime and Lumber Co., August 1910-October 1914.
  - Saxon Lime and Lumber Co with Giles County Lumber Co., December 1908-April 1912.
  - B. T. Johnson, et al, v. Tazewell Timber Corp. (3 files), August 1921-November 1923, March 1920-April 1926, January 1920-April 1926.
  - B. T. Johnson, et al (empty file).
  - Saxon Lime and Lumber Co., July 1908-June 1923.
  - Giles County Lumber Co., September 1906-September 1920.
  - Saxon Lime and Lumber Co., July 1912-August 1921.
  - Miller, Frank, Land Corp. v. Linkous and Shumate, December 1919-October 1922.
  - John B. Laing v. Empire Coal Land Corp., July 1914-November 1921.
  - State Highway (2 files), April 1921-November 1923, September 1922-May 1923.
  - Road Matters, September 1922-May 1923.
  - Buchanan County (2 files), August 1927-October 1928, undated.
  - Fidelity and Casualty Company of New York, October 1911-July 1921.
  - Buchanan County School Board v. F. M. Clevinger, et al, January 1920-July 1923.
  - Earnest, J. W., August 1917-July 1921.
- Box 21, 1916-1968 (Bulk, 1930-1968) (Box 21)
  - Lula May Albert, November 1933-June 1934.
  - Anderson, Theodore C., October-November 1935.
  - Allen, A. B., May-October 1940.
  - Atkins, Emmett L., April 1925-March 1926.
  - Ashton Land, undated.
  - Abstracts, November 1919-October 1929.
  - Bowyer, E. G., November 1933-June 1934.
  - Blankenship, J. Allen, April 1934.
  - Robert J. Bailey, July-October 1934.
  - Bowen, Alonzo, December 1933.
  - Berg, Rockford C., June-July 1940.
  - Blankenship, Otto, et al, September 1925-November 1933.
  - James M. Bane, undated.